Guide to the Bob Holman Audio/Video Poetry Collection 1977-2002 MSS.128
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Grassroots Poetry Videos, 1988-2001
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Urban Ritual, Undated; ID: 128.0417 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0417)
    - [1]-- Candlelight [2]-- Land/Scape [3]-- Wings of Fire, [1]--1993 [2,3]--1992; ID: 128.0418A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0418A)
    - Downset Surroundings, Undated; ID: 128.0419A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0419A)
    - Wayne Lammers 5 Music Videos, Undated; ID: 128.0420A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0420A)
    - Manifest Arts Poetry Video Series, 1990; ID: 128.0421 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0421)
    - A Poet In The House, 1993; ID: 128.0422 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0422)
    - 3 Poetry Slams at the Croc, Undated; ID: 128.0423 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0423)
    - CNN Poetry Slam Segment, 1993; ID: 128.0424 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0424)
    - Rise & Shine Productions/ The Dome Project Presents: For The Ed, Undated; ID: 128.0425 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0425)
    - The Poetry Video Learning Project: "Rooms of our Lives", 1986; ID: 128.0426 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0426)
    - Lonnie Shesher: [1]-- Cherokee Landing 1987 [2]-- S/Ding Central Hall 1986, [1]--1987 [2]--1986; ID: 128.0427A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0427A)
    - Gwen Gosé: "Short Shorts & Bell Bottom Bikinis" (Excerpts), 1994; ID: 128.0428 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0428)
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated; ID: 128.0429A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0429A)
    - Doug Knott's Small Dogs Bark 3, Undated; ID: 128.0430A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0430A)
    - Laurel Ann Bogen: "Wings/ That Which Takes Fight, Undated; ID: 128.0431A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0431A)
    - Toby Vann: [1]-- Continuum [2]-- Reservoir, Undated; ID: 128.0432 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0432)
    - Wayne Lammers, Undated; ID: 128.0433 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0433)
    - Ray McNiece - Promo Tape, 1994; ID: 128.0434A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0434A)
    - Jean Howard: [1]-- Women Without Children [2]-- The Light, Undated; ID: 128.0435 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0435)
    - Spoken War, Undated; ID: 128.0436A (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0436A)
    - Manuel Perez-Tejada: [1]-- The Morphing Poets [2]-- Walls of Haze [3]-- The Rituals of the Wind, Undated; ID: 128.0437 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0437)
    - tomandandy: Sound Image Reel, Undated; ID: 128.0438 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0438)
    - Rick Shapiro: Conan & Ceasar Salad, Undated; ID: 128.0439 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0439)
    - Mike McCallister: "Skinny Boys", 1994; ID: 128.0440 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0440)
    - Ellyn Maybe, Undated; ID: 128.0441 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0441)
    - Raymond Bally: "Outsider IBN", Undated; ID: 128.0442 (Box 21, Media ID: 128.0442)
    - Reno Roast, 1994; ID: 128.0443 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0443)
    - Michael McAllister: "Lift", Undated; ID: 128.0444 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0444)
    - Michael McAllister: "That Night", 1994; ID: 128.0445A (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0445A)
    - Edwin Torres in Berlin, [1994]; ID: 128.0446 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0446)
    - Edwin Only, [1994]; ID: 128.0447 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0447)
    - Willie Perdomo & Mike Tyler in Berlin, [1994]; ID: 128.0448 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0448)
    - 67985 #3, [1994]; ID: 128.0449 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0449)
    - [1]-- Willie Perdomo, Edwin Torres, Mike Tyler in Berlin 9/94 [2]-- Radio Fritz Interview, 1994; ID: 128.0450 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0450)
    - V. Katz: "Polyergus", 1993; ID: 128.0451 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0451)
    - Billy Lamont, Undated; ID: 128.0452 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0452)
    - Billy Lamont, Undated; ID: 128.0453 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0453)
    - Katie Soljak, Undated; ID: 128.0454 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0454)
    - #1 - Robert Mitchell, 1996; ID: 128.0455 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0455)
    - Jeff McDaniel: "Check the Bags", Undated; ID: 128.0456A (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0456A)
    - The Badger: Down With Jeff, Undated; ID: 128.0457 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0457)
    - Laurel Ann Bogen: "Wings/ That Which Takes Fight", Undated; ID: 128.0458 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0458)
    - The Psychic Poets Show, Undated; ID: 128.0459 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0459)
    - Wanted: X-Cheerleaders, 1994; ID: 128.0460 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0460)
    - Cosmic Rap, 1997; ID: 128.0461 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0461)
    - Video Graf 1, Undated; ID: 128.0462 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0462)
    - Lynne [Beyer] Memorial, Undated; ID: 128.0463 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0463)
    - Him, Them, Her, Undated; ID: 128.0464 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0464)
    - Kathe Burkhart: Performance Pescara Italy, 1995; ID: 128.0465 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0465)
    - Talking Headz, Undated; ID: 128.0466 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0466)
    - The Minneapolis Poetry All-Stars, Undated; ID: 128.0467 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0467)
    - Kei Kunihiro Poetry Reading, Undated; ID: 128.0468 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0468)
    - Andy Biskin: "The Big Flea", Undated; ID: 128.0469 (Box 22, Media ID: 128.0469)
    - Video Poetry, 1994; ID: 128.0470 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0470)
    - Lydia Lunch: "The Gun is Loaded", Undated; ID: 128.0471 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0471)
    - Video/ Poetry work by Kurt Heintz, Undated; ID: 128.0472 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0472)
    - Jean Howard: [1]-- Women Without Children [2]-- The Light, Undated; ID: 128.0473 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0473)
    - Nazi Youth in Brugge, 1997(Dub); ID: 128.0474 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0474)
    - Via Delle Cascine, Undated; ID: 128.0475 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0475)
    - Poetry Video: Larry Winfield, [1990, 1992]; ID: 128.0476 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0476)
    - Richard Loranger: [1]-- "TCS" [2]-- "in corpus flagranter", [1]--1997 [2]--1996; ID: 128.0477 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0477)
    - The Knitting Factory: The Last Poets, [1996]; ID: 128.0478A (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0478A)
    - Cross Talk, [1996]; ID: 128.0479 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0479)
    - Michel Negroponte: "No Accident", Undated; ID: 128.0480 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0480)
    - "Big": Tribe Magazine, Undated; ID: 128.0481 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0481)
    - The Bitter Poet - Solo, 1996; ID: 128.0482 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0482)
    - Highlights from The Bitter Poet Show, [1996]; ID: 128.0483 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0483)
    - Christian Vetz, Undated; ID: 128.0484 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0484)
    - The New Amazing Grace, 1994; ID: 128.0485 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0485)
    - Ambient Poet: Cari Griffo, 1997; ID: 128.0486 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0486)
    - Lo Maduro de la Cultura, 1994; ID: 128.0487 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0487)
    - Mouthsters 1997 Nat., ID: 128.0488 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0488)
    - Slam Skit '97, 1997; ID: 128.0489A (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0489A)
    - Kennon B. Raines: "Witch Goddess", Undated; ID: 128.0490 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0490)
    - Kennon B. Raines: "Witch Goddess", Undated; ID: 128.0491 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0491)
    - International Drag Poets Ball: "The Year Word Broke", 1996; ID: 128.0492 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0492)
    - Broken Meat, Undated; ID: 128.0493 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0493)
    - Poem in Action: Portarit of Vincent Ferrini, [1990]; ID: 128.0494 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0494)
    - we/eighteen, [1994]; ID: 128.0495 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0495)
    - Elemental: Being There, 1995; ID: 128.0496 (Box 23, Media ID: 128.0496)
    - "Messages To The Public'", 1989-1990; ID: 128.0497 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0497)
    - Mike Hazard, Undated; ID: 128.0498 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0498)
    - The Whole Shebang: "Poeting for Etheridge Knight", [1991]; ID: 128.0499A (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0499A)
    - Tama Mushi Iro: A Video Of Bug Haiku by Issa, 1996; ID: 128.0500 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0500)
    - Tiger Jack: Mr. Respect, 1998; ID: 128.0501 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0501)
    - The Match That Started My Fire: A film by Cathy Cook, 1991; ID: 128.0502 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0502)
    - [1]-- Border Brujo [2]-- Mi Otro Yo, Undated; ID: 128.0503 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0503)
    - Excerpts From 1001 Real Apes, Undated; ID: 128.0504 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0504)
    - F' loom: Language Music in Live Performance, 1997; ID: 128.0505 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0505)
    - Bob Holman - Digital Master from Carr Session, Undated; ID: 128.0506 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0506)
    - Apropoets, Undated; ID: 128.0507 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0507)
    - Chris Chandler: "Evil", Undated; ID: 128.0508 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0508)
    - Chocolate Kisses, Undated; ID: 128.0509 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0509)
    - End of Lizzie Borden, [1989]; ID: 128.0510 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0510)
    - Battle Sounds Turntablist Festival 1, 1996; ID: 128.0511 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0511)
    - Robert Priest, Undated; ID: 128.0512 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0512)
    - Words Aloud! The Poetry Slam, [1997]; ID: 128.0513 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0513)
    - …elle Senior Project, Undated; ID: 128.0514 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0514)
    - Michael Parker: "Don't Fall Off The Mountain", 1999; ID: 128.0515 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0515)
    - Correspondence: Shalom Gorewitz - 60 Minute Compilation, 1981-1998; ID: 128.0516 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0516)
    - Thai 98 I, [1998]; ID: 128.0517 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0517)
    - Thai 98 II, [1998]; ID: 128.0518 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0518)
    - Jim Northrup: With Reservations, 1995; ID: 128.0519 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0519)
    - Canada's Mid-Riff/ Nite 1, Undated; ID: 128.0520 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0520)
    - Japan, Undated; ID: 128.0521 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0521)
    - Letters Not About Love, 1998; ID: 128.0522 (Box 24, Media ID: 128.0522)
- Series VI: Spoken Word History, 1982-2001
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - "Off the Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol.1, Issue 1" [Part 1], 1991 (Media ID: 128.1023)
      Duration: [01:07:00]
    - "Off the Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol.1, Issue 1" [Part 2], 1991 (Media ID: 128.1026)
      Duration: [00:06:00]
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Poetry In Motion: A Film by Ron Mann, [1985]; ID: 128.0523 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0523)
    - Dial-A-Poet Television, Undated; ID: 128.0524 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0524)
    - Azul by Roland Legiardi-Laura, 1990; ID: 128.0525 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0525)
    - Azul, 1986; ID: 128.0526 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0526)
    - [1]-- New York Views [2]-- Gardens, Opera, Rock 'n Roll, [1991]; ID: 128.0527 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0527)
    - Off The Page: The First Video Poetry Magazine - Vol. 1 Issue 1, [1991]; ID: 128.0528A (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0528A)
    - The Battle of the Bards: The 9th Annual World Heavyweight Poetry Championship, [1990]; ID: 128.0529 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0529)
    - Great Moments From The Fifth Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1989; ID: 128.0530 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0530)
    - Baxter Black's 1st Video, 1991; ID: 128.0531 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0531)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #3 & #4, [1989]; ID: 128.0532 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0532)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #1 & #2, [1989]; ID: 128.0533 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0533)
    - Moyers: The Power of the Word - #5 & #6, [1989]; ID: 128.0534 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0534)
    - Moyers: Autry/ Toupe, [1989]; ID: 128.0535 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0535)
    - Voices & Visions 1: Elizabeth Bishop, 1988; ID: 128.0536 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0536)
    - Voices & Visions 2: Hart Crane, 1988; ID: 128.0537 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0537)
    - Voices & Visions 3: Emily Dickinson, 1988; ID: 128.0538 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0538)
    - Voices & Visions 4: T.S. Eliot, 1988; ID: 128.0539 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0539)
    - Voices & Visions 6: Langston Hughes, 1988; ID: 128.0540 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0540)
    - Voices & Visions 5: Robert Frost, 1988; ID: 128.0541 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0541)
    - Voices & Visions 7: Robert Lowell, 1988; ID: 128.0542 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0542)
    - Voices & Visions 8: Marianne Moore, 1988; ID: 128.0543 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0543)
    - Voices & Visions 9: Sylvia Plath, 1988; ID: 128.0544 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0544)
    - Voices & Visions 10: Ezra Pound, 1988; ID: 128.0545 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0545)
    - Voices & Visions 11: Wallace Stevens, 1988; ID: 128.0546 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0546)
    - Voices & Visions 12: Walt Whitman, 1988; ID: 128.0547 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0547)
    - Voices & Visions 13: William Carlos Williams, 1988; ID: 128.0548 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0548)
    - Fear and the Muse: The Story of Anna Akhmatova, Undated; ID: 128.0549A (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0549A)
    - Michael McClure & Ray Manzarek; "Love Lion", [1991]; ID: 128.0550 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0550)
    - Baxter Black 'Live On Public TV" - In Performance!, ID: 128.0551 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0551)
    - Kovac - Ruff, Undated; ID: 128.0552 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0552)
    - The American Poetry Review Presents Allen Ginsberg, 1988; ID: 128.0553 (Box 25, Media ID: 128.0553)
    - Philomene Long's The Beats: An Existential Comedy, Undated; ID: 128.0554 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0554)
    - At The Forks of Troublesome, Undated; ID: 128.0555 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0555)
    - Paris: "The Days of Old", 1992; ID: 128.0556 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0556)
    - Father's Daze: A Film By Mark Pellington, Undated; ID: 128.0557 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0557)
    - Mark Pellington: Public Enemy "Shut 'Em Down", Undated; ID: 128.0558 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0558)
    - Deep Fringe: The Anthology of the 1993 National Poetry Video Festival, ID: 128.0559 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0559)
    - The Poetry Film Sampler, Undated; ID: 128.0560A (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0560A)
    - The Sanders Report #16 - Nov 1993, ID: 128.0561 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0561)
    - Teachers & Writers Collaborative: "Determined To See The Far Land", 1990; ID: 128.0562A (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0562A)
    - The 17th Annual Poetry/ Film Video Festival Award Winners 1992/ 1993, ID: 128.0563A (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0563A)
    - The Language of Life With Bill Moyer: #101 Welcome To The Mainland, 1995; ID: 128.0564 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0564)
    - Ben Harper: Welcome to the Cruel World / Electronic Press Kit, [1993]; ID: 128.0565 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0565)
    - Cittee, Cittee, Cittee: The Poetry of Herschel Silverman, Undated; ID: 128.0566 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0566)
    - William Stafford and Robert Bly: A Literary Friendship, 1992; ID: 128.0567 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0567)
    - Eavan Boland - Lannan Literary Video #42, [1994]; ID: 128.0568 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0568)
    - Imprint - Show 3 - The Spoken Word: "Have You Heard The Word", 1994; ID: 128.0569 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0569)
    - Imprint: "Have You Heard The Word", [1994]; ID: 128.0570 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0570)
    - Todd Colby Variety Pak, [1]--1995 [2]--1993 [3]--1991; ID: 128.0571 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0571)
    - Dana Bryant on MTV Unplugged: "Heat", 1993; ID: 128.0572 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0572)
    - Hal Sirowitz on MTV's Spoken Word Unplugged, 1995; ID: 128.0573 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0573)
    - Hymnody of Earth, Undated; ID: 128.0574 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0574)
    - Sha-key: "Soulsville", Undated; ID: 128.0575 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0575)
    - Elizabeth Murray: Modern Woman, 1995; ID: 128.0576 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0576)
    - Reg E. Gaines: PSA - Mumia, 1996; ID: 128.0577 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0577)
    - McClure/ Hagedorn: Contemporary Voices '96, 1996; ID: 128.0578 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0578)
    - 1996 World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Troupe, Baca, ID: 128.0579 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0579)
    - 1996 Taos Poetry Circus - Global Voices: Coleman, Allen, ID: 128.0580 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0580)
    - 1997 Taos Poetry Circus - W.H.C.P.B.: Patricai Smith vs. Jimmy Santiago Baca, ID: 128.0581 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0581)
    - 1997 Taos Poetry Circus - Contemporary Voices: Peter Rabbit, Edward Dorn, ID: 128.0582 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0582)
    - American Poetry Literary Project (APL) on ABC News and Good Morning America, 1994; ID: 128.0583 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0583)
    - Murray Lachlan Young: MTV Networks Compilation, Undated; ID: 128.0584 (Box 26, Media ID: 128.0584)
    - Murray Lachlan Young: MTV Poet, Undated; ID: 128.0585 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0585)
    - Women of Hope: Latinas Abriendo Camino, [1996]; ID: 128.0586A (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0586A)
    - Nike Atheletes, 1997; ID: 128.0587 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0587)
    - Channel 4 Television: "Modern American Poets", Undated; ID: 128.0588 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0588)
    - Off the Page, Undated; ID: 128.0589 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0589)
    - The Best of Spike Jones, Volume Three, 1988 [Clips 1952-1957]; ID: 128.0590 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0590)
    - The Spike Jones Story, 1988; ID: 128.0591 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0591)
    - Lenny Bruce: The Lenny Bruce Performance Film, 1992 [Performance 1965]; ID: 128.0592 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0592)
    - Lenny Bruce without tears: a documentary (of a friend), 1992; ID: 128.0593 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0593)
    - Andy Kaufman: I'm From Hollywood, 1992; ID: 128.0594 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0594)
    - Andy Kaufman: Soundstage, Undated; ID: 128.0595 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0595)
    - Great Russian Writers: Vladimir Mayakovsky, Undated; ID: 128.0596 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0596)
    - The Cask of Amontillado, 1998 (Dub); ID: 128.0597 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0597)
    - 60 Minutes: Poetry Slam '99, 1999; ID: 128.0598 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0598)
    - ESPN - X Games, Undated; ID: 128.0599A (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0599A)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 1 "The Vigilant Island", 1994; ID: 128.0600 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0600)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 2 "Where The Edges of Conquest Meet", 1994; ID: 128.0601 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0601)
    - Aimé Césaire: Pt. 3 "The Strength To Face Tomorrow", 1994; ID: 128.0602 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0602)
    - Poetic Liscence: a short cut, Undated; ID: 128.0603 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0603)
    - God Told Me To, [1997]; ID: 128.0604 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0604)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 1, [1991]; ID: 128.0605 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0605)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 2, [1991]; ID: 128.0606 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0606)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 3, [1991]; ID: 128.0607 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0607)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 4, [1991]; ID: 128.0608 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0608)
    - The Best of Ernie Kovacs Vol. 5, [1991]; ID: 128.0609 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0609)
    - ESPN - X Games, Undated; ID: 128.0610A (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0610A)
    - X Games, Undated; ID: 128.0611 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0611)
    - Andy Kaufman: The Midnight Special, 1981 (Recorded); ID: 128.0612 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0612)
    - The Best of Spike Jones Volume One, 1985 [Clips 1952-1957]; ID: 128.0613 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0613)
    - The Best of Spike Jones Volume Two, 1987 [Clips 1952-1957]; ID: 128.0614 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0614)
    - The Generous Manas, [1995]; ID: 128.0615 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0615)
    - Poetry In Motion On Television, Undated; ID: 128.0616 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0616)
    - World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Sherman Alexie vs. Wanda Coleman, 1999; ID: 128.0617 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0617)
    - Andy Kaufman Plays Carnegie Hall, 1979; ID: 128.0618 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0618)
    - World Heavyweight Championship Poetry Bout: Alexie vs. Baca, 1989; ID: 128.0619 (Box 27, Media ID: 128.0619)
- Series VII: Spoken Word Video Filmed by Bob Holman, 1991-2002
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0620 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0620)
      Format: Video 8 mm
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0621 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0621)
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0622 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0622)
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0623 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0623)
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0624 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0624)
    - Public Poetry, 1992; ID: 128.0625 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0625)
    - All Star Slam! (One Angle), 1992; ID: 128.0626 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0626)
    - All Star Slam! (Hand Held), 1992; ID: 128.0627 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0627)
    - St. Mark's Poetry Project, 1992; ID: 128.0628 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0628)
    - Patricia Smith & Wanda Coleman, 1992; ID: 128.0629 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0629)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #1, 1992; ID: 128.0630 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0630)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #2, 1992; ID: 128.0631 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0631)
    - 100 Greatest Poets #3, 1992; ID: 128.0632 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0632)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #1, 1991; ID: 128.0633 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0633)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #2, 1991; ID: 128.0634 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0634)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #3, 1991; ID: 128.0635 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0635)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #4, 1991; ID: 128.0636 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0636)
    - First American Sign Language Literary Conference #5, 1991; ID: 128.0637 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0637)
    - [I Allen] 3/6/91, 1991; ID: 128.0638 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0638)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #1, 1992; ID: 128.0639 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0639)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #2, 1992; ID: 128.0640 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0640)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #3, 1992; ID: 128.0641 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0641)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #4, 1992; ID: 128.0642 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0642)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #5, 1992; ID: 128.0643 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0643)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #6, 1992; ID: 128.0644 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0644)
    - Cowboy Poetry Gathering #7, 1992; ID: 128.0645 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0645)
    - Alive I, [Early 1990s]; ID: 128.0646 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0646)
    - Alive II, [Early 1990s]; ID: 128.0647 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0647)
    - III Colby/ Holman, [Early 1990s]; ID: 128.0648 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0648)
    - Alive IV, [Early 1990s]; ID: 128.0649 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0649)
    - Ani De Franco / [Nowle Breedlue], Undated; ID: 128.0650 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0650)
    - Stop at Nothing, 1992; ID: 128.0651 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0651)
    - Eritrea I, 2000; ID: 128.0652 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0652)
      Format: MiniDV
    - Eritrea II, 2000; ID: 128.0653 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0653)
    - Eritrea III, 2000; ID: 128.0654 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0654)
    - Eritrea IV, 2000; ID: 128.0655 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0655)
    - Eritrea V, 2000; ID: 128.0656 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0656)
    - Eritrea VI, 2000; ID: 128.0657 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0657)
    - Eritrea VII, 2000; ID: 128.0658 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0658)
    - Eritrea IX, 2000; ID: 128.0659 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0659)
    - Eritrea X, 2000; ID: 128.0660 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0660)
    - Eritrea XI, 2000; ID: 128.0661 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0661)
    - Eritrea XII: Yemen, 2000; ID: 128.0662 (Box 28, Media ID: 128.0662)
- Series VIII: Poetry Slams, 1991-1994
  - Subseries A: Access Copies (Video)
    - SF National Poetry Slam - selects 9/93, 1993 (Media ID: 128.1005)
      Duration: 00:26:00
    - National Slam 1991 #1 (Media ID: 128.1027)
      Duration: 01:24:14
    - National Slam 1991 #2 (Media ID: 128.1028)
      Duration: 01:21:33
    - National Slam 1991 #3 (Media ID: 128.1029)
      Duration: 01:21:43
    - National Slam 1991 #4 (Media ID: 128.1030)
      Duration: 01:54:23
    - National Slam 1991 #5 (Media ID: 128.1031)
      Duration: 01:49:15
    - National Slam 1991 #6 (Media ID: 128.1032)
      Duration: 01:48:12
    - National Slam 1991 #7 (Media ID: 128.1033)
      Duration: 01:37:16
    - National Slam 1991 #8 (Media ID: 128.1034)
      Duration: 00:56:06
    - SF National Poetry Slam, September 1993 (Media ID: 128.1035)
      Duration: 00:33:15
  - Subseries B: Originals (Video)
    - National Slam 1991 #1, ID: 128.0663 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0663)
    - National Slam #2 1991, ID: 128.0664 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0664)
    - National Slam #3 1991, ID: 128.0665 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0665)
    - National Slam #4 1991, ID: 128.0666 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0666)
    - National Slam #5 1991, ID: 128.0667 (Box 29, Media ID: 128.0667)